### VIVEK VARDHAN

#### **BUSINESS ANALYST**

#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

To excel in any form of activity, professional or personal, that I undertake and to make a positive difference to the organisation with my presence. Business Analyst with 4.5+ years of experience and a proven knowledge of Data mining, cleansing and publishing reports.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### SENIOR BUSINESS ANALYST

Uber Technologies Ltd., Hyderabad, Telangana / Mar 2020 – Present

- Creating Dashboards for different driver partners on their weekly performance.
- Automating the Tagging/Untagging process of partners at city level.
- Worked on Vault Fraud detection of drivers.
- Automated weekly reporting process for different cohorts using Google script.

#### **SENIOR ANALYST**

Latentview Analytics, Bangalore, Karnataka / Jul 2019 – Mar 2020

- Working at client location (VMware Software Pvt Ltd) as a Senior Analyst, my work involved guiding sales representatives on the interoperability of different VMware products.
- Work involved collecting product version information from different data sources using SQL, cleanse the data using Python and figure out the latest version of a software for other software to work and establish product interoperability.
- End goal is to get valuable customers to get them upgraded to the latest version of VMware products and help in cross selling products.

#### CATASTROPHE DATA ANALYST II

AIG Analytics, Bangalore, Karnataka / Oct 2015 – Jul 2019

- Analysing commercial property data and generating useful business reports by utilising pre defined statistical methods.
- Deep dive analysis on different scenarios and providing in-depth analysis on losses and premiums to the stakeholders across US-CAN and London.
- Was a part of Data Steward team and played a crucial role in standardising/improvising the workflow.
- Played crucial role in collaborating the account and portfolio teams during roll-ups.

- vivekvardhan1512@gmail.co m
- **(**997) 244-7116
- ◆ C V Raman Nagar Bengaluru, KA, 560093

#### **EDUCATION**

# SRM UNIVERSITY Chennai, TamilNadu B.Tech Electronics and Instrumentation (May 2015)

## ADDITIONAL SKILLS

**SQL** 

Python

MS Excel

Google script

Power BI

**Basics of Machine Learning**